export const questions = [
  {
    key: 1,
    open: false,
    question: 'Lorem Ipsum',
    answer:
      'Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry.',
  },
  {
    key: 2,
    open: false,
    question: 'Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the',
    answer:
      'It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content of a page when looking at its layout. The point of using Lorem Ipsum is that it',
  },
  {
    key: 3,
    open: false,
    question: 'Where does it come from?',
    answer: 'pular belief, Lorem Ipsum is not simply random text. It has ro',
  },
  {
    key: 4,
    open: false,
    question: 'There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available',
    answer:
      'There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available, but the majority have suffered alteration in some form, by injected humour, ',
  },
  {
    key: 5,
    open: false,
    question:
      'Contrary to popular belief, Lorem Ipsum is not simply random text. It has roots in a piece of classical',
    answer:
      'It uses a dictionary of over 200 Latin words, combined with a handful of model sentence structures, to generate Lorem Ipsum which looks reasonable. The generated Lorem Ipsum is therefore always free from repetition, injected humour, or non-characteristic words etc.',
  },
  {
    key: 6,
    open: false,
    question:
      'Lorem Ipsum is not simply random text. It has roots in a piece of classical',
    answer:
      'There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available, but the majority have suffered alteration in some form, by injected humour, or randomised words which dont look even slightly believable. If you are going to use a passage of Lorem Ipsum, you need to be sure there isn t anything embarrassing hidden in the middle of text. All the Lorem Ipsum generators on the Internet tend to repeat predefined chunks as necessary, making this the first true generator on the Internet.',
  },
  {
    key: 7,
    open: false,
    question: 'It has roots in a piece of classical',
    answer:
      'Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry s standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book. It has survived not only five centuries, but also the leap into electronic typesetting, remaining essentially unchanged. ',
  },
  {
    key: 8,
    open: false,
    question:
      'The standard chunk of Lorem Ipsum used since the 1500s is reproduced below for those interested.',
    answer:
      'Many desktop publishing packages and web page editors now use Lorem Ipsum as their default model text, and a search for lorem ipsum will uncover many web sites still in their infancy.',
  },
  {
    key: 9,
    open: false,
    question: 'There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available',
    answer:
      'If you are going to use a passage of Lorem Ipsum, you need to be sure there isn t anything embarrassing hidden in the middle of text. All the Lorem Ipsum generators on the Internet tend to repeat predefined chunks as necessary, making this the first true generator on the Internet.',
  },
  {
    key: 10,
    open: false,
    question: 'Lorem Ipsum comes from sections',
    answer:
      ' Richard McClintock, a Latin professor at Hampden-Sydney College in Virginia, looked up one of the more obscure Latin words, consectetur',
  },
];
